[

{
"answer": "abstraction","question": "a simplified representation of something more complex. For example, a programmer can define functions to organize/clean up their code in order to reduce complexity and increase readability and efficiency"
},
{
"answer": "algorithm","question": "a precise sequence of instructions that can be executed by a computer to solve a problem"
},
{
"answer": "class","question": "a blueprint from which an object is instantiated. Defines the abstract characteristics of a thing, its attributes and its behaviors"
},
{
"answer": "constructor","question": "a special method that is called to instantiate an object of a class"
},
{
"answer": "function call","question": "a request that runs the code inside of a function"
},
{
"answer": "function definition","question": "a block of code that includes the keyword def followed by a name, any arguments that are required, code inside the function, and an output that is returned"
},
{
"answer": "for loop","question": "loops that repeat for a predetermined number of iterations"
},
{
"answer": "getter method","question": "a method that fetches data that is stored within an object. Provides information about the state of an object. Also known as an accessor"
},
{
"answer": "hex color","question": "a six-digit set of values ranging from 0 to F that specifies a color. The first two digits are the amount of red, the next two digits are green, and the last two digits are blue"
},
{
"answer": "IDE","question": "a developer’s workspace that provides programming tools and a space for coding. It stands for Integrated Development Environment"
},
{
"answer": "import","question": "a Python command that loads an external file and allows you to use new commands that are not built-in to Python. For example, random numbers or turtles"
},
{
"answer": "input","question": "information that is given to the computer by a user, usually typed text and mouse clicks"
},
{
"answer": "instance","question": "an object created from a class"
},
{
"answer": "instantiate","question": "the creation of an object (an instance) from a class"
},
{
"answer": "method","question": "a function that belongs to a class"
},
{
"answer": "object","question": "a data structure that contains attributes and behaviors. A software simulation/model representing an entity either physical (a box, a car, etc) or conceptual (a chemical process, a sale, driving directions, etc)"
},
{
"answer": "random()","question": "generates a random decimal number between 0.0 and 1.0"
},
{
"answer": "randint(a, b)","question": "generates a random integer between a and b"
},
{
"answer": "rgb color","question": "a set of three comma separated values ranging from 0 to 255 that specifies a color. The first value is the amount of red, the next is green, and the last is blue"
},
{
"answer": "setter method","question": "a method used to control changes to an object's internal state. Allows you to change the object’s data. Also known as a mutator"
},
{
"answer": "turtle","question": "a Python module that allows you to create drawings with code on a two dimensional plane. It is a Python version of an older language called Logo created by Seymour Papert for learning programming by controlling movement and drawing of an on-screen robot with commands such as forward(), left(), and pendown()"
},
{
"answer": "while loop","question": "loops without a predetermined end that either repeat until a condition is met or repeat forever"
},
{
"answer": "abstraction","question": "a simplified representation of something more complex. For example, a programmer can define functions to organize/clean up their code in order to reduce complexity and increase readability and efficiency"
},
{
"answer": "algorithm","question": "a precise sequence of instructions that can be executed by a computer to solve a problem"
},
{
"answer": "class","question": "a blueprint from which an object is instantiated. Defines the abstract characteristics of a thing, its attributes and its behaviors"
},
{
"answer": "constructor","question": "a special method that is called to instantiate an object of a class"
},
{
"answer": "function call","question": "a request that runs the code inside of a function"
},
{
"answer": "function definition","question": "a block of code that includes the keyword def followed by a name, any arguments that are required, code inside the function, and an output that is returned"
},
{
"answer": "for loop","question": "loops that repeat for a predetermined number of iterations"
},
{
"answer": "getter method","question": "a method that fetches data that is stored within an object. Provides information about the state of an object. Also known as an accessor"
},
{
"answer": "hex color","question": "a six-digit set of values ranging from 0 to F that specifies a color. The first two digits are the amount of red, the next two digits are green, and the last two digits are blue"
},
{
"answer": "IDE","question": "a developer’s workspace that provides programming tools and a space for coding. It stands for Integrated Development Environment"
},
{
"answer": "import","question": "a Python command that loads an external file and allows you to use new commands that are not built-in to Python. For example, random numbers or turtles"
},
{
"answer": "input","question": "information that is given to the computer by a user, usually typed text and mouse clicks"
},
{
"answer": "instance","question": "an object created from a class"
},
{
"answer": "instantiate","question": "the creation of an object (an instance) from a class"
},
{
"answer": "method","question": "a function that belongs to a class"
},
{
"answer": "object","question": "a data structure that contains attributes and behaviors. A software simulation/model representing an entity either physical (a box, a car, etc) or conceptual (a chemical process, a sale, driving directions, etc)"
},
{
"answer": "random()","question": "generates a random decimal number between 0.0 and 1.0"
},
{
"answer": "randint(a, b)","question": "generates a random integer between a and b"
},
{
"answer": "rgb color","question": "a set of three comma separated values ranging from 0 to 255 that specifies a color. The first value is the amount of red, the next is green, and the last is blue"
},
{
"answer": "setter method","question": "a method used to control changes to an object's internal state. Allows you to change the object’s data. Also known as a mutator"
},
{
"answer": "turtle","question": "a Python module that allows you to create drawings with code on a two dimensional plane. It is a Python version of an older language called Logo created by Seymour Papert for learning programming by controlling movement and drawing of an on-screen robot with commands such as forward(), left(), and pendown()"
},
{
"answer": "while loop","question": "loops without a predetermined end that either repeat until a condition is met or repeat forever"
},
{
    "answer": "setheading(angle)","question": "a Python turtle method that sets the turtle to face an angle: 0=East, 45=NE, 90=N, 180=W, 270=S. For example, this command with the argument (135) will point the turtle northwest."
},
{
    "answer": "towards(x, y)","question": "a Python turtle method that gets the angle from turtle's position to another position (x,y) or another turtle. For example, if the turtle is located at (0,0) then this command with arguments (0,10) would return 90."
},
{
    "answer": "setheading(angle)","question": "a Python turtle method that sets the turtle to face an angle: 0=East, 45=NE, 90=N, 180=W, 270=S. For example, this command with the argument (135) will point the turtle northwest."
},
{
    "answer": "towards(x, y)","question": "a Python turtle method that gets the angle from turtle's position to another position (x,y) or another turtle. For example, if the turtle is located at (0,0) then this command with arguments (0,10) would return 90."
}

]
